<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About Us on Welcome to LibreTechnica!</title>
    <link>https://libretechnica.github.io/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About Us on Welcome to LibreTechnica!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://libretechnica.github.io/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About LibreTechnica</title>
      <link>https://libretechnica.github.io/about/aboutus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libretechnica.github.io/about/aboutus/</guid>
      <description>LibreTechnica shares knowledge about technologies developed for the benefit of the commons. By promoting open-source technologies that are free from and resistant to corporate control, government censorship, political coercion, and environmental harm, we can together heighten and sustain the common good.
Our Mission #LibreTechnica&amp;rsquo;s mission is to encourage others to learn and adopt technologies for the benefit of the commons. Some example of our activities are: :
 Teaching people how to protect their privacy with secure messaging apps and email services Introducing computer users to the Linux operating system and other open-source software Promoting sustainable technologies, practices, and policies Helping small business and non-profit organizations implement free and open-source software for their infrastructure Supporting the deployment of independent, community-based network infrastructure  This mission supports our vision where the people have full knowledge and control over whom their data serves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seeking Contributors!</title>
      <link>https://libretechnica.github.io/about/contribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://libretechnica.github.io/about/contribute/</guid>
      <description>LibreTechnica is just starting out as a spin-off/superset of CryptoParty, the decentralized movement to share knowledge about protecting yourself in the digital space. If you are looking to contribute by writing some guides, designing graphics and branding, building a static site, or organizing, please reach out to us on Twitter @LibreTechnica. You can also post to General Project Discussion issues page.
 Mirrors #  github.com/LibreTechnica/libretechnica.github.io
  gitlab.com/LibreTechnica/libretechnica.github.io</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
